Trent Edilloran

Quality Assurance Intern

Computer science graduate with academic experience mainly developing in Java, C, C++, and Python. Experienced managing a team of customer service providers as well as handling the sensitive health information of millions of healthcare recipients. Currently collaborates between the business, engineering, and social media teams at Robot Cache as a quality assurance intern, ensuring an excellent customer experience of a video game distribution platform built on the blockchain.

Projects

Steam Web Scraper

Web scraper for obtaining game information from Steam store

Passwd as a Service

Network fetcher and parser for '/etc/passwd' and '/etc/group' files Fully functional multi-threaded shell with full I/O redirection

Tetris Clone

Javascript implementation of Tetris rendered within a browser Shell Prompt

Personal Info

Location

San Diego, CA

Phone

(619) 708-2647

E-mail

trent.edilloran@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/trent-edilloran

GitHub

github.com/tedilloran

Education

08/2012 - 05/2017

San Diego State University

Bachelor's of Science

Major - Computer Science

Minor - Japanese

Skills

macOS

Python	Javascript
React/Redux	Node.js
HTML	css
Java	C++
Git	Linux

Windows

Experience

02/2019 - Present

Quality Assurance Intern

Robot Cache

Works together with fellow interns in supporting the software engineering team in building a new video game distribution platform based on the blockchain. Contributes to the ongoing process of ensuring the developed software quality exceeds customer needs and desires by creating and executing test plans, reporting, reviewing, and documenting bug reports, and upon submitted bug fixes, repeating bug reporting process.

10/2018 - 02/2019

Account Administrative Representative

Kaiser Permanente

Assisted health purchaser contacts in the health coverage sales process by analyzing and resolving problems related to membership accounting. Maintained the membership enrollment database and researched tasks to support contract administration, cash operation control, medical record number assignment, and contracts and member I.D. card generation/ distribution.

05/2016 - 10/2018

Shift Leader

85C Bakery Cafe

Collaborates with a team of customer service providers to create an uplifting experience for customers and fellow associates in a fast pace environment. Daily responsibilities include managing associates, navigating individual customer requirements, baking and decorating breads and cakes with a high attention to detail, cash management, and adapting store experience to create a memorable connection with each quest.

10/2014 - 03/2015

Student Worker

San Diego County - Dept. of Housing & Community Development

Coordinated with a team of analysts in obtaining, verifying, and distributing funds towards numerous federal and state assistance agencies such as Housing Opportunities for Persons with AIDS and the Health & Human Services Agency. Responsibilities include assessing client satisfaction for completed housing work, verifying use of San Diego County granted funds, and evaluating applicant eligibility for financial or housing aid funded by a state and/or federal budget.

06/2014 - 08/2014

Business Intelligence Intern

Delivery Agent, Inc.

Supported the business intelligence team in maintaining and developing the online shopping experience for networks such as NBC, Fox, and Discovery. Duties included improving analytical tools, quality assurance testing (manual), back- end maintenance of tracking systems (excel), and building promotional emails for various networks (HTML, CSS, Dreamweaver).